[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Південь' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "みなみ"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Подорожувати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "りょこうします"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Чудовий' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "すてき"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Кораловий риф' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さん ご うす"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Рідкісний' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "めずらしい"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Правда' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ほんとう"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Окінава' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おきなわ"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Різноманітний' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いろいろ"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Схід' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とう"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'кльовий, класний, красивий' read in word?",
        "answer": "すばらしい"
    }
]
